alright guys in this video of course you can see by the title I want to start
好的家伙 在这个视频当然是 你 可以看到我想要开始的标题
talking to you guys about inheritance a very important concept in computer
关于 继承 一 说话 你们 计算机中非常重要的概念
programming especially with object-oriented programming so you're
编程特别是 面向对象的编程让你如此
going to be coming across that a lot so before I even get started talking about
要跨很多 要来得 这么 之前，我甚至 开始 说起
computer programming let's just talk about inheritance in real life what does it mean well I mean you can inherit like
计算机编程我们只是 说说 关于 现实生活中的 继承 是什么 它意味着我的意思是你可以继承像
um like specific genes from your parents so I inherited on my dad's eyes I
你喜欢父母的特定基因 所以我继承了我爸爸的眼睛
inherited my mom's nose and what that pretty much means is she passed those
继承了我妈妈的鼻子，那是什么 几乎意味着她通过了那些
traits on to me whenever they you know made me as a baby
只要你知道，就会对我有所了解 让我成为一个婴儿
and also there's another type of inheritance like when um I don't know
而且还有 另一种类型 继承就像我不知道的那样
like if your grandpa dies and you inherited his land it pretty much means
就好像你的爷爷去世了 继承了他的土地， 这几乎 意味着
that he gave his land to you so inheritance basically means getting
他把土地交给了你 所以继承基本上意味着获得
something from someone else that's the most simple definition so what the heck
从别人的东西是这样的 最简单的定义那么哎什么
could have mean in computer programming let's go ahead and make two classes
可能在计算机编程中有意义 让我们继续做两节课
we're going to make one class that's a parent and we're going to make another class that's a child and I'll show you
我们打算创建一个类 父母，我们要再做 一个 这是一个孩子，我会告诉 你
guys how the child can inherit or get stuff from the parent so of course they
伙计们 孩子如何继承 或得到 来自父母的东西当然是他们
don't have any land they don't have I color so let's go ahead and make some
没有任何土地 ，他们没有我 颜色 让我们继续 做一些
functions that they can inherit so what would on the parent do say print last
他们可以继承的功能 父母会说打印最后
name so of course this just looks like a normal class right now in my parents
当然这个名字看起来像是 一个 现在在我父母的正常班级
last name is the same of mine of course so Roberts so right now this parent
当然， 姓氏与 我的 名字相同 所以罗伯茨现在就是这个父母
doesn't have any cool land doesn't have a million dollars leave me all it has
没有 任何凉爽的 土地没有 一百万美元留给 我一切
this is lonely old function so I'm going to make another class right here and I'm
这是孤独的老功能，所以我要去 在这里建立另一个班级 ，我
going to name it child and just like before we can start building functions
将 它命名为孩子 就像 在我们开始构建功能之前
but check this out if you're wondering why do you have
但看看这个 如果你想知道为什么你有
these empty parentheses right here well in side these parentheses what you can pretty much type is the name of a class
这些空的括号就在这里 在这些括号中你能做什么 几乎类型是类的名称
that you want to inherit from so whenever I typed parent inside here what I'm telling Python is okay look for
你 要继承的 所以每当我在这里输入父母 我告诉Python的是好的
a parent class get everything inside that class then right now it's pretty
父类让一切都在里面 那个班， 那么现在它很漂亮
boring just one function and pretty much pass it on to your child so right now
无聊的只是一个功能，非常 所以，现在把它传递给你的孩子
even though it looks like this child class is empty it actually has in other
即使它看起来像这个孩子 class是空的，实际上是其他的
words it actually just inherited this print last name function so let's go
它实际上只是继承了这个词 打印姓氏功能让我们走吧
ahead and make one normal function in the child class I'll go umm print first name and this
提前做一个正常的功能 孩子班 我会打印 第一个名字和这个
will just be um it'll just be a normal function that belongs to the child and
只会是正常的 属于孩子的功能
it will just print out my first name which is buggy so check this out right
它会 打印出我的名字 这是错误的所以检查出来的权利
now it looks like there's one function and parent and one function and child
现在它看起来有一个功能 和父母和一个功能和孩子
but that's not actually how Python sees it well Python sees is this one function
但这实际上并不是Python 看到的 Python看到的就是这一个功能
parent and since this child inherited everything from the parent it actually
父母，因为这个孩子继承了 实际上 来自父母的一切
has print last name and print first-name don't believe me I wouldn't either
有打印姓氏和打印 名字 不相信我， 我也不会觉得要
because I lie about stuff a lot but in this case I am telling the true so I'll
因为我经常撒谎， 但在里面 这种情况我说的是真的 所以我会
make a function or excuse me an object called Buckey and it's going to be long
做一个函数或原谅我一个对象 叫做Buckey ，它会 很长
to that child class now check this out if I put Buckey come on you're stupid
那个孩子班现在检查一下 如果我把Buckey加上你是愚蠢的
freaking carpal tunnel glove I can do print first name and we already know
我能做的吓坏了腕管手套 打印名字，我们已经知道
that because the function is right in that class but did you know I can also
因为功能 正确 那个班，但 你知道 我也 可以
do print last name and check this out I'm going to run it and it's going to
打印姓氏并检查出来 我要去运行它 ，它会去
print Bucky which is just a normal function and also Roberts which is a
打印Bucky这是 正常的 功能和罗伯茨这是一个
function that it inherited from the parent so that's the basics the very
它继承自的功能 父母，所以这是基本的
basics of inheritance pretty much saying okay what class do you want to get stuff
继承的基础知识几乎说 好吧，你想要什么课程的东西
from so pretty much doesn't literally do this but goes that class copies
从这么几乎不是字面意思 这个， 但是那个班级副本
everything and paste it right in child simple enough guys understand it good
一切都贴在孩子身上 简单的人都明白它很好
because now I'm going to talk to you guys about something that's a little bit
因为现在我要跟你说话 关于某事的人
more advanced a little bit more confusing so right now we have print
更先进的多一点点 令人困惑， 所以我们现在 有印刷品
lastname basically as a child function that it inherited now what we can also do is we can also have the option of
lastname 基本上作为 子函数 它现在继承了我们也可以 做的是我们还可以有选择
overriding overriding wow that's a for some reason hard for me to say the child
压倒一切的 哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇 我有点难以说出这个孩子
can override that function so what we can do is this def print last name and
我们可以覆盖那个功能 能做的就是这个def print 姓氏 和
also I'll just like I don't know make this print something called schnitzel
我也只是喜欢我不知道make 这印刷品称为炸肉排
burg so I got to tell you guys a story real quick because I don't have a therapist and I've been meaning telling
burg所以我得告诉你们 一个故事 真快， 因为我 没有 治疗师，我一直在说
this for a long time to get it off my chest
这个很长一段 时间来得到它我 胸部
but basically whenever my parents had me they put Roberts on the birth
但基本上每当我的父母 拥有 我 他们让罗伯茨出生了
certificate and that was my last name for a while growing up Roberts
证书 ，这是我的姓氏 一会儿长大 他妈的 罗伯茨
Bucky Roberts in high school however arm I found out that my mom was actually a
然而，Bucky Roberts在高中时手臂 我发现 我的妈妈实际上是一个
monkey and I was embarrassed about it so I ran away from home I joined the circus
猴子和我很尴尬 我离家出走了，我加入了 马戏团
and I changed my last name to schnitzel burg so even though I inherited the name Roberts later on in life I decided to
我把我的姓改成了炸肉排 burg 所以即使 我 继承了这个名字 罗伯茨后来在生活中我决定
over ride it to schnitzel burg so this is also an option in Python so check
过来骑到炸肉排这样的 也是Python中的一个选项，所以检查
this out even though I inherited this function to
这个 即使我继承了这个功能
begin with I have the option of overriding it and basically in order to
从我可以选择开始 覆盖它基本上以
do that you create a same function with the same exact name and what this says
这样做，你创建一个具有相同的功能 同样的确切名称和这 说的
is okay we're practically going to replace this with whatever you decided
还好 我们几乎要 用你决定的任何东西取而代之
to do here so that is a little story about my life and that is also how you
这里做的就是一个小 故事 关于我的生活，这也是你的方式
can inherit something but you have the choice overriding it or if you don't you
可以继承的东西，但你有 选择压倒它还是你不喜欢它
can just use the normal function as well so now you guys understand in the next
也可以使用正常功能 所以现在你们明白了
tutorial I'm going to talk to you guys about multi
教程我要和 你们 谈谈 关于多
full inheritance so we get even more complex but it's actually going to be a
完全继承 所以我们得到更多 复杂，但它实际上将 成为一个
pretty cool maybe I'll think of another fake story to tell you guys but for now
非常酷， 也许我会想到另一个 假的故事告诉你们，但是 现在
then guys for watching don't forget to subscribe and I will see you guys later
那些观看的人不要 忘 了 订阅，我稍后会见到 你们